mobicow.com 2018-02-24

# Mobicow | Privacy Policy

What this policy covers?

This policy covers business contact information, such as name, email address, telephone number and address and other work-related information, that visitors provide to Mobicow online on publicly available Mobicow sites.If you are a business enrolled in advertiser programs that are subject to the Advertiser Master Services Terms and Conditions, Insertion Order(s) or other advertising or marketing agreements . 

Types of information we collect and how we use it:

The following describes what information Mobicow Advertising Solutions collects from visitors to the Mobicow sites as well as outside the Mobicow network of web sites, and how we may use it: 

Email addresses and related information

There may be opportunities for visitors to the site to sign-up to receive email communications. Visitors may subscribe by providing an email address and other requested information. Recipients of email marketing messages will have the opportunity to unsubscribe from future messages via the link(s) provided within the message. 

Cookies and web beacons on Mobicow web sites

All browsers offer “cookies” and if you permit their use, they will store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to the site that placed the cookie. A cookie is a small text file. It is not a program, or a plug-in. It could not be used as a virus, and it cannot access your hard drive. Cookies simply assist in tracking which features you like the most and allow content to be customized upon your return, according to prior preferences at that site. They would not gather or hold any personal information. The information collected by these third-party advertising companies through the use of these web beacons is not personally identifiable. In addition to the above, Mobicow’s email delivery vendor may employ web beacons and cookies within HTML email messages sent on our behalf and on the Mobicow sites. The use of cookies and web beacons described above help Mobicow to measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use the Mobicow sites. 

Promotions and sweepstakes

From time to time, Mobicow may sponsor or host promotions and sweepstakes where we collect information. Use and sharing of this information will be disclosed in promotion and sweepstakes rules or on the page where you sign-up. 

IP addresses and information specific to your computer

Mobicow logs IP information when you visit our sites, including the Mobicow sites. In addition to this information, Mobicow collects information that your computer’s browser automatically reports to us such as information about your operating system and browser version. 

Fraudulent Activity

Fraudulent Activity on Mobicow must result from genuine user interest. Any method that artificially generates clicks or impressions on your Mobicow is strictly prohibited. These prohibited methods include but are not limited to repeated manual clicks or impressions, using robots, automated click and impression generating tools, third-party services that generate clicks or impressions such as paid-to-click, paid-to-surf, autosurf, and click-exchange programs, or any deceptive software. Please note that clicking on your own ads for any reason is prohibited. Failure to comply with this policy may lead to your account being disabled. To Know more about Account Disability. 

Security Measures

We protect the personal information you share with us. For example, if you make an online transaction with us, We preserve all the information you provides to us. Access to your personal information is limited to people who need it to do their job. Authorized third-party agents may also need access to some of your personal information, But We do not otherwise share your personal information with third parties, unless you have granted us permission to do so. We may collect and possibly share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of ‘s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

Policy Updates

All updates to this policy will be posted here. Contact at: info@mobicow.com to aid in processing your request, please include the following details: Contact information (your name, address, e-mail address, etc.) Name of the program where you want the update applied Details of the request (e.g. change of e-mail address, unsubscribe from a newsletter, review of personal information, etc.) Note: This policy also covers the personal information you provide to Customer Support.
